<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Persephone Station Logs</title>
  <subtitle>The journal of a space case</subtitle>
  <link href="https://psl.ahov.co/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://psl.ahov.co/"/>
  <updated>2022-01-30T06:37:17Z</updated>
  <id>https://psl.ahov.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Alexis Hovorka, Amity Fulmer, and Carolynn Chang</name>
    <!--email>alexisspacegirl@gmail.com</email-->
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>PSL 1266-4 Dean Stafford</title>
    <link href="https://psl.ahov.co/0003/"/>
    <updated>2022-01-29T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://psl.ahov.co/0003/</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This was a huge mistake.</p>
<p>When I first boarded this station, I expected a peaceful trip. Just a few
months of space travel, no biggie. I did not expect for all j}l} to break loose, and I’ve really started regretting
my life decisions as a result. Don’t get me wrong, I’m all for a touch of
adventure here and there, but I did <em>not</em> sign up for this level of danger. All
the <6HL¢V;'4` |xK 8l$04#(Gfle< 6∆ who knows
where, and I’m U=&B.&π #gx>'&j¶_i</p>
<p>There’s not much I can do at this point besides wait, for the end or for rescue
I have no ∆J'ZAC~ clue. Farewell…</p>
<p>No.</p>
<p>This <em>can’t</em> end here. I won’t allow it! I’ll make it to Mars if it’s the last
vbxx∆~* thing I do!</p>
<p>I’m not a coward. You’ll see, father.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>PSL 003-1452</title>
    <link href="https://psl.ahov.co/0002/"/>
    <updated>2022-01-28T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://psl.ahov.co/0002/</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today, three separate lighting control boards gave up the magic blue smoke. That’s the 3rd month in a row that’s happened… on the 3rd of the month. I wouldn’t put it past Devin to break stuff and give me more work to do, but I don’t think he could stomach that much fun and coordination. Not like it bothers me. It takes 10 minutes to fix, assuming he’s not breathing down my neck. He should’ve sabotaged the comm network. Now that would’ve been a challenge. But again, coordination.</p>
<p>Seth acted like it was an omen, that ‘great tragedy will soon befall Persephone’ or some shit. I laughed along, but he insisting that there was more to it – just to tease me, of course. I said it was just a coincidence, but he just kept waving that stupid sandwich in the air and babbling about numbers. What a dork.</p>
<p>Because they obviously don’t mean anything. Bonnie sneezed like 7 times in a row the other day, but you don’t see me trying to find some secret code or message in it. The ‘message’ was that she was sniffing Genny too much when the peppercorns were nearby.</p>
<p>I wish ÷}u'; 5O)NS £J Hs¢N that.</p>
<p><img src="https://psl.ahov.co/images/cycler-orbit.png" alt="Image of Persephone Station cycler orbit" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>2105-03-13 Intro</title>
    <link href="https://psl.ahov.co/0001/"/>
    <updated>2022-01-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://psl.ahov.co/0001/</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I’ve never had a personal log before.  Like, I’ve heard all that stuff about
how journaling is supposed to be good for you psychologically and whatever, but
every time I’ve tried to get ih;{ 8* * yept it up
for like a week at most. Sectan requires us to keep one, though, probably for
some baseline morale metric, so maybe this time will be different?</p>
<p>I’m glad it’s encrypted—all they can see is that I’m <em>making</em> entries, and
roughly how long they are, not what they say. &#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;&#x2588;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
</feed>
